<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Entries on Dan Has Plan</title>
    <link>http://danhasplan.com/entries/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Entries on Dan Has Plan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 14:15:09 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://danhasplan.com/entries/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>I Have Plan</title>
      <link>http://danhasplan.com/entries/i-have-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 14:15:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://danhasplan.com/entries/i-have-plan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guys, Arkansas sucks.&lt;/strong&gt; But before I go and start offending &lt;em&gt;everybody&lt;/em&gt;, let&amp;rsquo;s address the proverbial elephant in the room. This &amp;ldquo;blog&amp;rdquo; is called Dan Has Plan. I live in a car that is conveniently named an &amp;ldquo;Element&amp;rdquo; and so while it would be &lt;em&gt;facile&lt;/em&gt; to adopt an obvious title riffing off of various puns about elements and how I may or may not be in one, I would not stoop so low. Moreso, and let this be the bottom line:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I have plan.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back to Arkansas, but let&amp;rsquo;s start with Memphis. Memphis is the current domain of THE Griffin Smith. Patient Zero, one might say. In visiting a Griffin Smith, one can only spend so much time in a Griffin Smith&amp;rsquo;s house before ze begins to &lt;em&gt;be&lt;/em&gt; a Griffin Smith in mind, body, and spirit (not a &lt;em&gt;bad&lt;/em&gt; thing, just a &lt;em&gt;different&lt;/em&gt; thing), and this is important for the visitor to know because, much like death by carbon monoxide poisoning, &lt;em&gt;becoming&lt;/em&gt; a Griffin Smith is a subtle but effective process. Signs of the transformation include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Asking for just one bite or sip&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Watching TVs that are on the ceiling with no issue whatsoever&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sprawling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Waking up early and asking that all other Griffin Smiths do the same&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fastidiously organizing half of one&amp;rsquo;s things&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being an exemplary friend &amp;lt;3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wearing criminally loose socks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And humans are not the only vectors for this transformation&amp;ndash;non-humans are susceptible as well. It was clear that in this particular Griffin Smith&amp;rsquo;s house there were at least five others living there as well (I believe that two lived in the crawlspace beneath the house).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, when one begins to &lt;em&gt;be&lt;/em&gt; a Griffin Smith, ze begins to think like one, and therefore becomes receptive to ideas like making the first destination of a life-changing and deeply significant Road Trip &lt;strong&gt;Hot Springs, Arkansas&lt;/strong&gt;. Decisions like these are not necessarily wrong, but they are certainly not correct. And it is here that I would like to confess to an infliction of my own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I have no plan and in this I have lost all control.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may find that the words of this &amp;ldquo;blog&amp;rdquo; are contradictory, but you must not accept it. In the particularly relevant words of George Orwell, it will be necessary &amp;ldquo;to forget whatever it [is] necessary to forget, then to draw it back into memory again at the moment it [is] needed, and then promptly to forget it again.&amp;rdquo; In this &amp;ldquo;blog&amp;rdquo; we will &amp;ldquo;use logic against logic&amp;rdquo;, and we will not even know it, as it will be purely emotional. Case in point: to arrive in Hot Springs is to leave Hot Springs. Like after two hours because damn that place has some &lt;em&gt;vibes&lt;/em&gt;. Get out and stay vibes. Become us and live to die vibes. Nuh-uh. Let&amp;rsquo;s go to Houston.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>